Gala Concert
あれ？
（かをり）くう…　痛て…。
（かをり）♪♪「タン　タタンタン
タン　ターン　タタンターン」→
Gala Concert
Huh?
What?
（凪）終わりました。
I'm done.
（紘子）ほら　行けよ。　先生。
Go on. Do your job as a teacher.
忌憚ない　ご意見を。
Your honest opinion, if you will.
手加減　すんなよ。
Don't hold back, all right?
（公生）ふん。
Holding back? What's that?
（公生）フォルティッシモと
ピアニッシモは　はっきりさせて。
Make the difference between
fortissimo and pianissimo clearer.
And count the rests properly.
（公生）休符も　しっかり数えて。
You keep making faces, your posture is terrible,
and don't grit your teeth like this is a pain to play!
眉間に　しわがよってる。
姿勢が悪い。
（凪）うう～。
苦々しく　歯を　食いしばらない！
左手のリズムの流れが
遅れてる。
The rhythm of your left hand is coming in late.
My hands are small, so my fingers can't reach right away.
手が小さくて
すぐに指が届きません。
手首を動かして弾くんだよ。
Move your wrist to reach those notes.
１拍目
最初の指を小指で弾いて→
Play the first beat with your pinky.
and then use that momentum to bring your wrist over.
その勢いで　手首を使って
こう　弾きやすい位置に…。
And move like this.
（紘子）３３３小節目のペダル
変えたら？
How about changing the way you pedal at measure 333?
That won't help me win.
それでは　勝てません。→
譜面は　完璧です。
すなわち　神。
The score is absolute!
To put it simply, it's sacred!
We are but servants who worship it.
われらは　神に仕える下僕。
Was she always like this?
《こんな子だっけ？》
（紘子）《キャラ　変わった？》
Did her personality change?
Only egotistical people who have given up on winning would ignore the score.
（凪）楽譜の指示どおり
弾かないなんて→
勝つことを放棄した
人間のエゴです。
《君の人生で　ありったけの君で
真摯に弾けばいいんだよ》
Just play with sincerity, and put your all
into giving the performance of a lifetime!
楽譜は神じゃないよ。
完璧でもない。
The score isn't sacred.
It's not absolute, either.
人間が生み落とした
とても感情的なものだ。
It's just an extremely emotional
piece of work created by humans.
That's why it clings to you, like shackles.
《だから　しがらみのように
付きまとう》
陳腐ですね。
グサッ！
What a cliché.
Spouting nonsense like that is exactly what brought you down.
（凪）そんな　甘っちょろいこと
言ってるから→
神から人間に　落ちちゃうんだ。
《レッスンまで　時間あるな》
There's still some time before the lesson.
I was just thinking that I hadn't heard your voice lately.
《最近　声　聞いてないなーって
思って》
《あっ　そうだ。
お菓子　買わなきゃ…》
Oh, right.
I should buy those sweets.
《君の好きな　カヌレを…》
Those canelés that you like so much.
《心の準備も　していないのに→
It's always when I'm the least ready to see you that you appear before me, without warning.
いつも　君は
ふいに現れる》
Oh!
誰だっけ？
《記憶喪失！？》
Who are you again?
Are you suffering from amnesia because you hit your head?
《頭　打ったから！？》
Nag nAg NaG nag Nag nAg NaG nag Nag nAg NaG nag Nag nAg NaG nag Nag nAg NaG nag
Oh, excuse me. It's been forever since I last saw you.
すみませんねえ。
最近　顔　見なかったもので。
見舞いにも来ないし
薄情者は影も薄い。
You never come to visit. I've thrown aside your cold heart long ago!
I was just—
これから…。
ねー　ねー　渡君は？
Hey, where's Watari?
I've been out here waiting for him.
渡君　待ち伏せしてんだけど。
Watari's...
渡は…　まだ　学校にいるよ。
He's still at school.
He was in the classroom earlier.
さっきまで　教室に…。
I'm so forgiving, you could call me an angel.
私は　天使のように優しい。
薄情者の君に
贖罪のチャンスを与えよう。
As cold as your heart may be, I'll give you another chance to thaw it out.
君を代役に任命します。
I'm appointing you as his substitute.
君でいいや。
I guess you'll do.
かばんも大きいようで。
And you do have a spacious bag.
Eh
heh
Seasonal Apparel
（女性）わー　カワイイ！
So cute!
Seasonal Apparel
このカワイイの　私の～！
This cute one's mine!
私のカワイイの
引っ張らないで～！
Don't tug on my cute clothes!
あの…　僕　レッスンが。
Um...
I have a lesson.
はっ！
カワイイ～　秋の新作だ。
Oh!
Adorable! It's the new one for fall!
This stationery is adorable!
カワイイ！　レターセット！
メールで　いいんじゃない？
Just stick to texting!
Hey, she's lost!
迷子だー！
何で楽しそうなの！？
Is that something to be thrilled over?!
[ﾏｲｸ]（アナウンス）迷子のお知らせを
致します。
This is a customer announcement for a lost child.
Miyuki!
≪（母親）みゆき！
Mommy!
Oh, you!
もう～！
困った人を見つけると
ほっとけないのよね～。
Can't just ignore someone in need when you come across one!
ふんっ。
《嘘つき！》
Liar!
Heavy
お母さん　泣いてたね。
Her mom was crying, wasn't she?
Yeah. She must've been really worried.
うん。　すごく　心配してたんだよ。
でも　お母さんや　お父さんを
泣かせちゃ駄目だよ。
But you shouldn't make your parents cry.
When I held that little girl's hand, she squeezed back really hard.
あの子ね　手をつないだら
ぎゅーって握ってくるの。
超　カワイイ。
It was so adorable!
絶対　離さないでって感じ。
It was like she was saying, "Don't let go, no matter what!"
きっと　離したら
一人　取り残されそうで→
I bet she was scared that if I did let go, she'd be left behind and on her own.
怖かったんだね。
あっ　これ　君のジュース。
Oh, here.
Your drink.
ああ　持たせっ放しだった。
Oh, I've had you holding onto that all this time.
あ～あ。
Jeez.
She's in her uniform, so she came to school today.
《制服…　今日　登校したんだな》
《僕の心配は
杞憂に終わったんだ》
It looks like I was worrying over nothing.
Huh?
あれ？　君　かばんは？
Where's your school bag?
ああっ！
取りに行こう。
Let's go get it.
Seto
遅～い！
（紘子）ピアノ　たたかない。
He's late!
Don't take it out on the piano.
公生は　来ないよ。
（凪）えっ！？
Kousei's not coming.
What?!
He just texted me.
さっき　メール　来た。
（凪）言ってください！→
You should've told me!
Are you really okay with such
irresponsible behavior, Ms. Seto?
いいんですか？　瀬戸先生。
こんな不真面目な態度。
（紘子）あんたさあ　やけに
公生に　突っ掛かるけど　何で？
Hey, why are you always so quick to lash out at Kousei?
あっ…　ヤダ～　瀬戸先生を
とられたくなくて→
Oh, no! I just don't want to lose you to him, that's all.
私　つい～。
I don't know what you're trying to pull here,
（紘子）何が目的か知らないけど→
もし　公生に
危害を加えでもしたら→
but if you ever put Kousei in danger,
あたしが　ぶっ殺してやるわ。
I'll put an end to you.
Wow, I didn't know people cared this much about Arima Kousei.
へえ～　愛されてますね。
有馬　公生。
あたしの息子だもん。
He's like a son to me.
（凪）じゃあ　どうして　私を
迎え入れてくれたんですか？
Then,
why'd you take me as a student?
公生に
何かをくれると思ったから。
Because I thought it would give Kousei something.
（紘子）《悲しみ以外の何かを》
Something other than sorrow.
Are you sure you can trust the enemy?
（凪）敵を信用していいんですか？
（紘子）敵？　あんた　敵なの？→
Enemy? You're his enemy?
Aren't you a fellow musician following the same path?
音楽の道を
共に歩む者じゃないの？
（紘子）あら
上手に描けてんじゃない。→
Wow, that's really well-drawn!
Go and show Nagi too.
お姉ちゃんにも　見せてあげな。
（小春）うん。
（小春）ウフフ…　はい！→
Here!
ウフフ…。
（紘子）《悲しみは
もう　たくさんだ》
He's faced more than enough of sorrow.
（紘子）公生には
幸せなピアニストになってほしい。
I just want Kousei to become a happy pianist.
Wow! It's so dark!
わあ～　真っ暗。　不気味～。
How creepy!
かばんを学校に置いてくるなんて
二度手間。
You're making life harder for yourself, leaving your bag at school.
Doorway
Shiho
Ryouta
かばんは？
Where's your bag?
Over here, maybe?
えっと…。
こっちかな？
いや　こっちだったかな？
No, maybe it's over there.
嘘か！　嘘ついたんか！
ひいいいい。
You lied?! Did you lie to me?!
My bag isn't here at school...
かばんは　学校にありましぇん。
Come to think of it,
《そういえば…
昼間から　かばん持ってなかった》
she didn't have it with her in the afternoon, either.
今日　登校してたんだよね？
You came to school today, right?
今日　一日だけ
外出させてもらったの。
They let me out of the hospital just for today.
ごめん。　どうしても
学校に　来たかったの。
Sorry.
I wanted to come here no matter what.
My memory was getting a little hazy.
忘れちゃいそうだったから。
僕の方こそ　ごめん。
I'm the one who should be sorry.
代役じゃなくて
渡がよかったね。
You should've had Watari, not a substitute.
せっかくの　一日だったのに。
I mean, it was your one day out...
君は忘れるの？
Are you going to forget?
学校を探検した女の子を。
The girl you explored the school grounds with.
一緒に　迷子を助けた女の子を。
The girl you helped rescue a lost child.
病院を抜け出して
待ってた女の子を。
The girl who snuck out of the hospital and waited for you.
君は忘れるの？
Are you going to forget about her?
《その人の心に
ずっと住めるように》
So that I can live in their hearts forever.
《ここにいる人たちは→
The people here will never forget us.
私たちのことを
忘れないでいてくれる》
I'll never forget this.
《私…　忘れない》
I won't forget.
忘れない。
I won't forget, even if I die.
死んでも　忘れない。
うん。　やっぱり　君でよかった。
Right.
I'm really glad it's you.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ちょっと　疲れちゃった。
I'm just a little worn out.
学校の備品で　２人乗りは
まずいね。
Riding double on a school bike might've been a bad idea.
バレたら　怒られるね。
We're in trouble if we get caught, huh?
Sorry about your lesson.
ごめんね　レッスン。
平気だよ。
No big deal. This is Hiroko we're talking about.
紘子さんだし　許してくれるよ。
She'll forgive me.
無駄な一日なんかじゃないよ。
It wasn't a meaningless day.
It was a really wonderful day, so much that I wish time would just stop still.
このまま　時間が止まっちゃえって思うくらい　すてきな一日だった。
ありがとう。
Thank you.
お買い物して
夜の学校を探検して→
I went out shopping and then explored the school at night.
男の子に送ってもらう帰り道は→
Now, there's a boy who's giving me a ride back home,
all while the stars above us are shining brightly.
こんなに
星が　キラキラしてるんだね。
Is it because it's chilly out?
＜肌寒いせいかな。
交わす言葉が温かい＞
The words we exchange feel so warm.
＜余計に　君を近くに感じる＞
It makes you seem all the more closer.
＜渡の代役でも　何でもいい＞
I'll be Watari's substitute or anything that you want,
＜ずっと　このまま…＞
as long as we can stay like this forever.
I couldn't ask her the reason
＜僕は　その涙の訳を→
Your Lie in April
聞けなかった＞
for those tears.
Your Lie in April
Too slow. The tempo starts lagging
because you're not playing it in one go.
遅い。　そこ　一気に弾かないから
テンポがずれる。
I'm pissed.
Pissed
（凪）《イラッ！　やってんじゃん。
目いっぱい　速く弾いてんじゃん》
Pissed
But that's just what I'm doing. I'm playing it as fast as I can.
（凪）《これ以上　できるか》
Pissed
I can't play it any faster!
This is how you do it.
Pissed
だから　こんな感じで。
Like this.
You damn robot!
この　機械野郎がー！→
Don't play it like it's so easy!
さらっと　弾いてんじゃねー！
（凪）《フ…　フフフ…》
（紘子）じ～。
はっ。
聞いてた？
Have you been listening?
はっ　はい！
Y-Yes!
I hate feeling incompetent.
（凪）《無能は嫌い》
Okay then, let's get this part down.
じゃ　ちょちょいと
やっちゃおう。
But I hate Arima Kousei even more.
（凪）《有馬　公生は　もっと嫌い》
（さつき）凪～　上山先輩
振ったんだね。
Nagi! You turned down Kamiyama, didn't you?
（小麦）もう　何人目よ。
How many does that make?
Break his glasses
Poison
Assassination Plan
Important!
Break his glasses
Well, I can't stand guys who've
got glasses and that literary vibe.
（凪）だって　文系眼鏡野郎
嫌いだもん。
Break his glasses
Poison
Anyway, did you decide what you're doing for the school festival?
（さつき）それより
学祭の演目　決めたの？
（凪）まだ。
Not yet.
The festival's in November.
（小麦）学祭　１１月だよ。
そろそろ　準備しとかないと。
We should start getting ready for it.
We're allowed to invite guests from outside the school.
（さつき）外から　ゲスト呼ぶのも
ありなんでしょ？　ＯＢとか。
Like alumni, right?
I hear Miike's bringing in someone famous.
（小麦）三池君は
大物　呼ぶらしいよ。
I don't have time for that right now.
（凪）今は　それどころじゃないよ。
Arima Kousei, I'll find a way to make you kiss my feet!
（凪）《有馬　公生…　あいつを
どうやって　屈服させるか》→
《フフッ　フフフ…》
（さつき）おぞましい腐臭。
FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU
She's brewing up an evil plan!
（小麦）だだ漏れだ。
FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU FU
It's reeks of it.
But our festival's known for its top students' unique performances, you know.
（小麦）でも
うちの学祭といえば→
成績上位者が
ユニークな演目を　準備するって→
注目されてるんだよ。
You're usually fired up for that kind of stuff, Nagi.
（さつき）凪が燃えそうな
シチュエーションじゃん。
Top students...
（凪）《成績上位者…》→
That's right. I'm the angel of Kurumi Junior High.
《そうよ。
私は　胡桃中のエンジェル》→
《それなのに…》
（小麦・さつき）天狗！
And yet...
Is that a tengu?
Seto
Why am I getting yelled at?!
（凪）《何で　怒られなくちゃ
いけないのよ！》
速い！　速く弾こうとして
上滑りしてる。
Too fast. You're making careless
mistakes because you're rushing.
それじゃ　フォルテにならない。
You can't sound out a forte out like this.
うわ～ん！
Huh? She ran off!
ああ　逃げちゃった。
≪（紘子）追い掛けな。
えっ？
Go after her.
Huh?
あんたの役目よ。　公生。
That's your job, Kousei.
（凪）《しょうがないじゃん。
手が小さいんだから》
What am I supposed to do?
My hands are small.
≪ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
紘子さんの　言ったとおりだ。
It's just as Hiroko said.
（凪）ふん！
あっ。
Hmph!
Um, sorry about that.
あの…　ごめんね。
その…　人に教えるの初めてで。
I've never taught anyone before.
Here, a peace offering.
これ　おわびに。
（凪）《芋で懐柔されるか！》
You think you can win me over with a sweet potato?!
It's so good and it'll melt in your mouth. Not to mention, it's a Beniazuma!
おいしそうだよ。　とろとろだよ。
紅あずまだよ。
Yum!
はっ！
（凪）《芋に膝を屈しちゃった》
I caved in for a sweet potato!
ここ　よく来るの？
Do you come here a lot?
I used to play here all the time.
昔　よく遊んでもらったんです。
私のヒーローに。
With my hero.
Come on, Nagi! I'm gonna leave you behind!
（男の子）《早く来い　凪！
置いてくぞ！》
（凪）《待ってよー！》
Wait up!
He was the one who started playing the piano first.
（凪）もともと　ピアノも
その人が始めたんです。→
だから　その人を追い掛けて　私も。
So I followed in his footsteps.
You like him.
好きなんだ。
But he's completely focused on someone else.
（凪）でも　その人は　私以外の人に
夢中なんです。→
そのせいで　今
迷って　悩んで→
And because of that, I feel lost and confused.
I'm trapped in a dark labyrinth, deep inside my heart.
真っ暗な　心の迷路にいる。
だから　気付いてほしい。
私がいるって。
That's why I want him to notice that I'm here
私のピアノで…。
with my playing.
（凪）《何で　こんなこと
話してるんだろ》→
Why am I saying all this?
《よりによって
にっくきピアニストに…》
And of all people, to the pianist that I hate.
不純な動機でしょ？
Talk about ulterior motives, right?
Most meetings have one, you know.
きっかけなんて　そんなもんさ。
（凪）《誰かに　吹き飛ばして
ほしかったのかもしれない》→
I might've wanted somebody to help me shake off
《ピアノに対する負い目を》
this obligation I feel toward playing the piano.
Rock, paper,
（公生・凪）じゃんけん　ぽん！
scissors!
P-I-N-E-A-P-P-L-E!
いきますよー。
Let's go!
Rock, paper,
（公生・凪）じゃんけん　ぽん！
scissors.
（凪）有馬先生は
好きな人　いないんですか？
Isn't there anyone you like?
Two in a row!
いないよ。
（凪）嘘です。→
There isn't.
G-L-I-C-O!
There is someone. It's written all over your face.
いるって　顔に書いてある。
どんな人なんですか？
Rock...
Paper...
What kind of person is she?
Scissors!
そんなはずないよ。
だって　その人は→
That can't be true.
C-H-O-C-O-L-A-T-E.
Because she's...
僕の友達を好きな
女の子なんだ。
a girl who's into a friend of mine.
（凪）それって
諦める理由になるんですか？
And that means you have to give up on her?
G-L-I-C-O.
愛より友情ですか。
Picking friendship over love?
What a cliché.
陳腐です。
Yeah, you're right.
うん　そうだね。
でも　僕には
これが　精いっぱいなんだ。
But this is the best I can do.
C-H-O-C-O-L-A-T-E.
What kind of person is she?
（凪）どんな人なんですか？
She's...
その人はね
ジェットコースターみたいな人なんだ。
This girl is like a roller coaster.
Crying, laughing.
泣いたり　笑ったり。
僕は　振り回されてばかり。
She's got me hanging on tightly at every bend.
その人がいるだけで→
With her presence,
モノトーンだった世界が
カラフルになるような→
she gave color to my monotone world.
She's a really dazzling,
とても　まぶしくて
とても　強い人なんだ。
really strong person.
Hey! Did you forget the canelés?!
こらー！　カヌレ　忘れたんかー！
So heartless! You even promised me!
薄情者！　約束してたのにー！
売り切れてたんだよ！
They were sold out, okay?!
Premium
Sweet Bean Jelly
Azuki
Premium
Sweet Bean Jelly
Azuki
Premium
Sweet Bean Jelly
Azuki
Premium
Sweet Bean Jelly
Azuki
（渡）俺が　おいしい甘味を
買ってきたよ。
Premium
Sweet Bean Jelly
Azuki
Well, I brought you something that could pass for canelés!
まあ　渡君。
Oh, Watari!
I can't disagree that Arima is slacking off.
（柏木）確かに
有馬は　たるんでる。
中学１年の女の子に
ピアノを教えてるんだって。
I hear he's teaching piano to a first-year girl.
（渡・椿）はあ！？
（渡）見損なったぞ　紹介しろ！
What?!
Introduce her to me!
（椿）何で　柏木が
そんなの知ってんの！？
How do you know that, Kashiwagi?!
椿に相談したって→
Even if I brought this up with you, it's not like you're an expert on the subtleties of girls.
女の子の機微は　分からないだろ？
今　何つった？
ごめんなさい。
Grind
What did you say?
Sorry!
Grind
なめとんのかー！
Are you messing with me or what?!
Hiroko forced me to!
紘子さんに　押し付けられたんだ。
僕だって　嫌なのに。
I don't even want to do it!
キスマーク！
（渡）あっ！
A hickey?!
（椿）よからぬことしてんのは
お前だー！
You're the one indulging in unsavory acts!
ギャー！
どんなレッスン　してんのよ！
Just what kind of lessons are you giving her?!
No fair, Kousei! Getting a jump on...
ずるいぞ　公生。　抜け駆け。
Do you really think you have the time to teach someone?
人に教えてる暇なんか
君にあるの？
いや　だって　紘子さんが…。
また　言い訳。
Like I said, Hiroko's...
Excuses! You don't have time to waste chasing after girls!
女の子と　イチャイチャする
時間なんて　ないでしょ！
If you've got so much time on your hands, why don't you practice more?
そんな暇　あるなら
もっと　練習に　あてたら？
I'm doing my best teaching her.
一生懸命　教えてるよ！
And when I get home, I do my own practicing!
家に帰ったら
自分の練習もしてる！
And I'm telling you, that's not enough!
それじゃ足りないって　言ってんの！
ちょっ…。
Hey...
You're wasting your own time while teaching!
教えてる時間
無駄にしてるじゃん！
Other people are practicing more!
他の人は　もっと練習してるよ！
危機感がないんだ！
Don't you feel any pressure?
だから　じゅうぶん　やってるよ！
I told you, I'm practicing enough!
Fit in more practicing!
じゃあ　もっと　やりなよ！
じゅうぶんなんて　ない！
There's no such thing as enough!
１２月には　コンクールが
始まるんだよ！
The competitions are going to
start up in December, you know.
Do you actually think you still have time?
まだ　時間があるとでも
思ってんの！？
Before you know it—
あっという間に…。
あれ…。
Oops...
アハハ…　何か
変なスイッチ　入っちゃった。
Everything just rushed to my head and took over.
Sorry.
ごめん。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい。
（凪）《ウフフ　お前の信用は
地の底まで失墜するぞ》→
Everyone's trust toward you is going to plummet straight to the Earth's core, Arima Kousei!
《有馬　公生》
（さつき）ねえ
何か　いいことあった？
Hey, did something nice happen to you?
（凪）えっ　何で？
Huh? Why do you ask?
The notes from your piano are skipping.
ピアノの音が　スキップしてる。
But you know notes can't skip.
音が　スキップするわけ
ないじゃん。
そう言われると
そうなんだけどさ。
Well, you can go ahead and say that.
でも…　うん。
But, still...
やっぱ　スキップしてる。
I think they're skipping.
《僕の友達を好きな
女の子なんだ》
She's a girl who's into a friend of mine.
（凪）《あんな　かい性なしじゃ
駄目ね》→
I don't see it happening for a hopeless wimp like him.
No way will things work out.
《絶対　報われない》→
《ちょっとだけ
ほんの　ちょっとだけ→
But we might...
We might be just the tiniest bit alike.
似ているかもしれない》→
We're both pursuing people who will always be out of our reach, no matter how hard we try.
《あがいても報われない相手を
追い掛けて　見詰めて→
Our gazes fixed on them, welling with burning affection.
恋い焦がれている》→
I'm trying to destroy Arima Kousei.
《私は　有馬　公生を
たたきつぶそうとしている》
（凪）《崇高な犠牲》
（凪）ただいま～。
It's a noble sacrifice.
Aiza
I'm home!
A love that seeks nothing in return.
（凪）《見返りを求めぬ愛》
Aiza
Hey, you're home.
≪おう　おかえり。
You're early, Nagi.
（武士）早かったな。　凪。
I am the phantom,
（凪）《われは　ファントム。
オペラ座に潜む怪人》
like the phantom who lurks in the opera house.
ただいま。　お兄ちゃん。
I'm home, Brother.
やあ。
Hey.
お見舞いは？
あっ。
Did you bring anything?
I... I forgot.
忘れた。　ごめん…。
Sorry...
心配して　来てくれたんだ。
You've been worrying about me, huh?
変だったもんね　私。
I was acting pretty weird.
《似てない》
They aren't alike.
《はじかれたように笑ったり→
Bursting into laughter without warning, getting hysterical over trivial things,
ささいなことで
ヒステリックに　わめいたり→
突然　泣きだしたり
すごく　優しくなったり→
crying out of the blue, suddenly turning gentle,
何かを諦めたり→
or giving up whatever they had.
僕の近くにいた人が
そうだった》
Someone close to me was just like that.
《似てない。
似てなんかいない》
She's not like her. She's nothing like her.
《嘘だ。　嘘だ。　嘘だ》
It's not true.
"You really are a strange person."
あなたって　本当に変な人。
My Sweet Accomplice     Mita Masahiro
病院に　お見舞いに来たのに→
"You came all the way to the hospital to see me, but you haven't said a word."
ずーっと
黙り込んでいるんですもの。
My Sweet Accomplice     Mita Masahiro
あたしと　心中しない？
"Will you come with me to find out how it ends?"
Episode 16
Two of a Kind
Episode 17
Twilight
sore zore no yume wo erande
No two dreams can be the same
Episode 17
Twilight
sore zore no yume wo erande
No two dreams can be the same
Watch next week too!
Two people on one bicycle is forbidden by law.